{
  "quiz_one" : [
    
    {
      "question": "Handlebars: What is Handlebars primarily used for?",
      "answer": "Template creation",
      "choices": ["Template creation","Back-end development","Database management","DOM manipulation"],
      "feedback": "Correct answer is 'Template creation', which highlights Handlebars as a tool for generating HTML templates efficiently."
    },
    {
      "question": "CSS: What property is used to change the text color of an element?",
      "answer": "color",
      "choices": ["font-color", "text-color", "color", "style"],
      "feedback": "Correct answer is 'color', which is used to set the text color of an element in CSS."
    },
     {
        "question" : "HTML: Choose the correct HTML element for the largest heading:",
        "answer" : "<h1>",
        "choices" : ["<h1>","<H>","<header>","<heading>"],
        "feedback" : "Correct answer is <h1>"
    },
     {
        "question" : "HTML: Choose the correct HTML element to define important text",
        "answer" : "<br>",
        "choices" : ["<i>","<important>","<br>","<strong>"],
        "feedback" : "Correct answer is <br>"
    },
     {
        "question" : "HTML: Which character is used to indicate an end tag?",
        "answer" : "/",
        "choices" : ["^","*","/","<"],
        "feedback" : "Correct answer is /"
    }

  ],
  "quiz_two" : [
     {
        "question" : "Java is a _______ language.",
        "answer" : "OOP",
        "choices" : ["OOP","Proecdural","Functional","Scripting"],
        "feedback" : "Correct answer is OOP"
    },
     {
        "question" : "Java: How do you insert COMMENTS in Java code?",
        "answer" : "// This is a comment",
        "choices" : ["/* This is a comment","// This is a comment", "# This is a comment"],
        "feedback" : "Correct answer is // This is a comment"
    },
    {
      "question": "HTML: How do you write comments in HTML?",
      "answer": "<!-- comment -->",
      "choices": ["// comment", "<!-- comment -->", "/* comment */, <= comment =>"],
      "feedback": "Correct answer is <!-- comment -->, which is the syntax for adding comments in HTML."
    },
     {
      "question": "JavaScript: What does the || operator do?",
      "answer": "It performs a logical OR operation",
      "choices": ["It concatenates strings", "It performs a logical OR operation", "It compares two values", "Function declaration"],
      "feedback": "Correct answer is that it performs a logical OR operation, returning true if at least one of the operands is true"
    },  
     {
        "question" : "Java: The value of a string variable can be surrounded by",
        "answer" : "False",
        "choices" : ["Single Quotes","Double Quotes","Both Single and Double Quotes","None of the above"],
        "feedback" : "Correct answer is Double Quotes"
     }
  ]
}